[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
DON'T TOUCH ME!
BARNEY: I think you dropped this
back in Black Mesa.
Right on! Now, just give me a
ski mask and we're good to go.
[microwave beeping]
Ha-haa!
SCIENTIST: My God!
Oh, yeah! All Mars, all the time!
So, these are drugs, right?
Only one really fast way to find out.
Aaaaahhh...
WHOO-HOO-HOO!
So. We meet at last.
[crying]
Hey, I want a raise; I just
saved the Statue of Liberty.
MAN: I've got work to do.
DID YOU HEAR ME?
I SAID THE STATUE OF LIB--
Look! A rock! It's amazing!
This is my bucket. There are
many like it, but this one's mine.
GET OFF THE ROAD, YOU STUPID GIT!
Ah, good.
Now, I need you to
listen to me very carefully.
You are to address me as DOCTOR Freeman.
I think I might be color blind.
Who's a good doggy? Are you?
WAAAAHHH-AAAAH-AAAAAAAAAH!
JESUS! MARDI GRAS IS
FUCKING CRAZY THIS YEAR!
Bee-de-beep-de-beep-bop-beep-bop.
I don't understand. There's no
known physics model for this.
Unless...
OH MY GOD! I'M TWO-DIMENSIONAL!
Mm! Kat-Patty.